Soon, you'll lose all your power.
Once you lose the power you were granted,
you'll realize you're nothing at all.
Sooha...
- The Moon Altar -
Damn you!
Sooha!
Sooha, wake up! Sooha!
We need to get out of here.
We can't leave.
Is this light the unsealed royal power?
And that's trapping her in here?
Sooha...
There's something I haven't told you yet.
That night, I was scared
to death to bite your neck.
I didn't know what I'd do if I hurt you.
But more than that, I was
happy to learn you trusted me.
So I promise I'll repay your trust
by getting you out of here now.
Heli.
Sooha?
Heli, you... you came to my rescue again.
Both then and now, you're always...
You're always...
Yeah.
Heli!
Both then and now,
you're always getting in my way!
If it weren't for you,
the princess would've chosen me!
Heli!
At least, she would have in this life!
Stop!
Heli, hang in there! Get up!
Why? I can't get out!
Heli, hang in there!
Your Highness.
It's all over now.
Everyone who came to
save you is out of strength.
And I've still got plenty of underlings.
The power you granted
them has returned, too.
In the end, all of it will be mine.
Everything will be taken from you,
and you will be mine forever.
Dardan!
I have no strength left...
Sooha, I have to protect you.
You healed our wounds.
You shared your power with us, too.
So why can't I do anything for you now?
Without the power you
granted me, I'm useless.
Don't waste your time.
Will you flee and be reincarnated
again? Just try it.
No matter how long it takes or
where you hide, I will find you.
Haven't you ever thought it was strange?
Why were you always suspected
of being a vampire?
Why were the people around you
always attacked by vampires?
You know, Sooha...
Chris died because of you.
Because you cared for him
more than anyone else,
I planned everything so
I could take his spot.
You understand me now, don't you?
Even if you escape me now, you'll just
meet the same fate in your next life.
Dardan!
It's too late.
You used the last of your power.
You still don't know
how to use it properly.
You don't deserve it.
That's why I'll take it from you.
I know I can use it far better than you.
Rest for a while.
I'll end this in the meantime.
My power should be gone, so why?
I'd been keeping it secret.
I hid that both vampire and
werewolf blood flowed in my veins.
But even after I admitted it,
they're still my friends.
This power was meant to be used
to save both them and Sooha, but...
I wasn't happy when I first
realized I had this power
because I didn't understand why I had it.
Now I understand that it's not for
hurting others, but for protecting them.
So why can't I use it?
Normally, I'd be able to
get up there in an instant.
Will I never move like that again?
I have to save Sooha.
I can't believe I'm powerless
in this critical moment.
Damn him. Damn him.
Damn him for doing this to Sooha.
I wish I could hit him as hard as I can.
But...
Damn, damn, damn!
I hate this.
I don't want to lose anyone I care about.
I need to protect them, so why can't I?
I was afraid of the dark
when I was little.
But at some point,
I stopped feeling that way.
The darkness is my domain.
Shadows are a part of me.
I have to save the others.
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
Heli!
I'm so close!
I'm so close to the end!
Heli, are you okay? Heli!
Noa, how did you use your power?
I'm not sure myself.
I thought I couldn't use it anymore.
But for some reason, I felt
like I'd always had this power.
No, wait.
I know I sensed it.
I wasn't granted this power by Sooha.
That's it.
Remember what Marge said?
That we're vampire lords.
Yeah.
Our crests haven't
disappeared, which means...
we still have our powers that awakened
after we became vampire lords.
We must've forgotten
about our true powers.
Yeah.
Remember!
Heli?
Heli regained his power.
Guys, listen to me.
We all have powers we've always had.
Remember that.
Now I will be king!
Shion!
Don't let them take her!
Slay your allies!
Marge, are you okay?
Yes. Thank you.
Sooha!
This ends now!
How have your powers returned?!
Damn you, werewolf!
Enough...
What?
Enough.
I...
I'll end this.
Jaan!
I don't need any of it anymore.
Not the princess's power,
nor the princess herself.
If I can't live with the princess,
then I don't mind dying with her.
What is he doing?
Sooha!
Your Highness, I'll be
with you at the end.
That's right. Before that...
I'll take care of you.
Sooha, why again?
Sooha! Sooha!
I know. We'll just do it again.
You'll be reborn, and we'll meet again!
No matter how many millennia
it takes, I'll find you!
I swear I'll look for you!
Heli, I'm sorry.
I can't reincarnate again.
This is the end of my life.
Meeting all of you in this life,
befriending you,
and spending our time together...
It made me so happy.
So it's okay.
Since this is the end,
I won't hide anything anymore.
I love you, Heli.
I love you too, Sooha.
Heli.
In both the present and the past, you've
been the greatest knight of my life.
Your Highness, I will always
be your knight, and yours alone.
So this is the princess's power.
You don't know how to use it properly!
Damn it...
Dardan, now that I've regained all
my power, I cannot forgive you.
Your crimes are far too great.
Your Highness, all I wanted was your love.
Do you know how hard I,
a man of low status, had to work
to climb to the chancellor's seat?
I did it all for your love.
If only you'd loved me!
Then I never would've done any of this!
I told you.
Only a citizen who's sincerely
pledged their loyalty
can inherit the royal power.
It can never be claimed by those
who try to take it by force.
Love is the same.
I knew.
I knew my love wouldn't
go the way I wanted.
Despite knowing your heart
wasn't mine from the start...
No, because I learned that...
I used status as an excuse.
Despite knowing that,
no matter how hard I tried,
I simply couldn't change
how I felt about you.
Selen, you will always be my...
Your Highness...
No, you're a queen now, Your Majesty.
Please, just call me Sooha.
But...
Allow me to formally
thank you for finding them.
I simply did what I had to do.
Guys, thanks for coming to save me.
What will you do now?
Both the kingdom and Dardan are gone now.
I think I'd like to live
my own life in the present.
I have good news.
A new dorm room has opened up.
You can move into it.
Really? Thank you.
It must've been tough
living in that old room.
The new rooms are shared,
so be nice to your roommates.
Roommates...
You...
Uh, um...
You're so strong!
I-I just thought I'd clean under the bed.
I'll help.
Hup.
Oh, right. The screw on this bed—
Sooha.
Heli!
Guys!
We came to help.
Thanks for coming, but there
isn't that much to do.
I know. Shall we have some tea?
Yes, let's.
If you insist.
Happy birthday, Khan!
Here, for you!
Thanks.
Sooha, you came!
Have fun today.
Okay!
Ugh, how am I supposed to have fun?
I just got here, and I'm already bored.
Sooha, we don't have
time for this. Let's go.
We only invited Sooha!
What are you guys doing here?!
Well, you guys ruined our birthday party!
Just leave your presents and go!
You just want the presents!
Khan will appreciate them!
Thanks for inviting me today.
I'm glad you came.
Are you and Heli getting along?
Yeah.
Sooha, like I told you before,
werewolves love whoever we see
during an eclipse for life.
So I'll love you forever, too.
But that's not all.
I really do like you.
I'm glad you were the one
I ran into that night.
I want you to be happy.
Thanks, Khan.
So you're the great Sooha.
My name is Luca.
It's an honor to meet you.
Forgive my brother.
I am Louis, the younger twin.
Luca, Louis! When'd you get here?
Sorry we're late.
Excuse us, Your Majesty.
From now on, we shall stand by your
side and protect you, Your Majesty.
Oh, uh, I'm not a queen anymore.
I'm just a high school student.
Cheers!
It's so dark. Give us a light, Jino.
I'm not a flashlight.
Hey, when's the last time
you guys used your powers?
When I roasted marshmallows for Sooha.
During nightball practice?
To catch the ball Jaan threw outside
the academy with his monstrous strength.
To make a crab silhouette.
None of that sounds very useful.
What about you, then?
When I made the art club
draw portraits of me.
Don't use it for that!
I haven't used mine at all since then.
Yeah, 'cause you can't
do anything fun as a wolf.
When you put it that way, Heli
probably uses his telepathy the most.
Were you two just speaking telepathically?
Since when?
What were you talking about?
W-We weren't talking about anything.
Really?
Hey, Heli.
Tell us.
It's a secret.
What? Sooha, your face is bright red.
Huh?!
C'mon, what were you talking about?